<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UQCS</title><link>https://uqcs.org/</link><description>Recent content on UQCS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 22:37:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uqcs.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hackathon 2021</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 22:37:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2021/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2021 Friday 10th September &amp;ndash; Sunday 12th September
49-200 (Friday), 49-301 (Saturday &amp; Sunday).
Get your tickets now! Facebook event The much awaited UQCS Hackathon is back &amp; better than ever! Taking place from the 10th to 12th of September, this is a great time to learn a new framework, develop your programming and/or design skills, and win some money. Use the link above to buy tickets - make sure to buy them before 22nd August to get a LIMITED EDITION Hackathon 2021 t-shirt for ONLY $5 and early bird tickets for only $10!</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2021</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 08:44:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2021/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2021 (Presented by IMC) 10am &amp;ndash; 4pm, Saturday 20th March The UQCS CodeJam is an individual competitive programming competition hosted each year to put students' programming and problem solving abilities to the test. You'll be given a list of questions to solve, varying in difficulty, with solutions to harder questions earning more points and the highest scoring competitors taking home some sweet prizes. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of fields but all can be solved with the help of code.</description></item><item><title>Hackathon 2020</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:43:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2020 5pm Friday 16th October &amp;ndash; 8pm Sunday 18th October Get your tickets now! Facebook event Howdy, y'all! We're happy to announce our biggest event of the year, the UQCS Hackathon, will be on October 16th to 18th in Room 301 of the Advanced Engineering Building.
Form a team on Friday night, then spend two days building something cool &amp;mdash; a game, a website, hardware, the sky's the limit.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://uqcs.org/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 01:34:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/code-of-conduct/</guid><description> This is the UQCS Code of Conduct &amp;ndash; the set of rules that govern the behaviour of members of the society both in person and on our various online social platforms. Proposals for changes can be made through the submission of issues to this GitHub repository by members of the society.</description></item><item><title>Constitution</title><link>https://uqcs.org/constitution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 01:34:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/constitution/</guid><description> This is the UQCS constitution &amp;ndash; the set of rules that govern the society. Any changes to the constitution must be requested and voted on at a General Meeting. Proposals can be made through the submission of issues to this GitHub repository by members of the society.</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2020</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 12:16:23 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2020 (presented by Atlassian) 10am &amp;ndash; 3:30pm, Saturday 28th March Contest now open on HackerRank.
Sign up to compete and get on the leaderboard! The UQCS CodeJam is an individual competitive programming competition. You get a list of questions to solve varying in difficulty, with harder questions gaining more points. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of fields but all can be solved with the help of code.</description></item></channel></rss>