<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UQCS</title><link>https://uqcs.org/</link><description>Recent content on UQCS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:43:00 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uqcs.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>hackathon</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:43:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2020 5pm Friday 16th October &amp;ndash; 8pm Sunday 18th October Get your tickets now! Howdy, y'all! We're happy to announce our biggest event of the year, the UQCS Hackathon, will be on October 16th to 18th.
If you aren't familiar with how the UQCS Hackathon works, it's pretty simple:
Form your team Build something cool Eat Free Food Present what you have made Win prizes In the past people have built websites, desktop apps, games, hardware, and even robots and if you've never been to a Hackathon before, don't worry as we'll be running a talk beforehand walking through what to do at your first Hackathon.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://uqcs.org/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 01:34:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/code-of-conduct/</guid><description> This is the UQCS Code of Conduct &amp;ndash; the set of rules that govern the behaviour of members of the society both in person and on our various online social platforms. Proposals for changes can be made through the submission of issues to this GitHub repository by members of the society.</description></item><item><title>Constitution</title><link>https://uqcs.org/constitution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 01:34:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/constitution/</guid><description> This is the UQCS constitution &amp;ndash; the set of rules that govern the society. Any changes to the constitution must be requested and voted on at a General Meeting. Proposals can be made through the submission of issues to this GitHub repository by members of the society.</description></item><item><title>codejam</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 12:16:23 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2020 (presented by Atlassian) 10am &amp;ndash; 3:30pm, Saturday 28th March Contest now open on HackerRank.
Sign up to compete and get on the leaderboard! The UQCS CodeJam is an individual competitive programming competition. You get a list of questions to solve varying in difficulty, with harder questions gaining more points. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of fields but all can be solved with the help of code.</description></item></channel></rss>