<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Competitions on UQCS</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/</link><description>Recent content in Competitions on UQCS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 12:44:31 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uqcs.org/competitions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hackathon 2023</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:50:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2023/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2023 Friday 25th August &amp;ndash; Sunday 27th August
49-301, Advanced Engineering Building.
Get your tickets now! Facebook event Get ready for UQCS's biggest event of the year: Hackathon! Bring your ideas, teammates and coding passion to hack it out over the weekend. This year we will have many free meals (exact number to be confirmed) and the ability to stay overnight at UQ so that you can code deep into the night uninterrupted.</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2023</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:57:47 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2023/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2023 (Presented by IMC Trading) 10am &amp;ndash; 4pm, Saturday 1st April The UQCS CodeJam, our semester 1 flagship event, is an individual competitive programming competition designed to put the programming and problem solving abilities of students of all years to the test. You'll be given a list of questions to solve, each varying in difficulty and style, with harder questions earning more points. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of disciplines but can all be solved with the help of code.</description></item><item><title>Hackathon 2022</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 20:21:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2022/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2022 Friday 26th August &amp;ndash; Sunday 28th August
49-301, Advanced Engineering Building.
Get your tickets now! Facebook event Form your teams, brainstorm your cool ideas, and get ready to eat tons of free food... UQCS Hackathon 2022 is here!! Featuring prizes bigger and better than ever, SEVEN free meals, and 24 hour stay (TBD)! That's right - you'll be able to stay at uni overnight to get that authentic hackathon experience (TM).</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2022</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 21:45:32 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2022/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2022 (Presented by IMC) 10am &amp;ndash; 4pm, Saturday 2nd April The UQCS CodeJam, our semester 1 flagship event, is an individual competitive programming competition designed to put the programming and problem solving abilities of students of all years to the test. You'll be given a list of questions to solve, each varying in difficulty and style, with harder questions earning more points. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of disciplines but can all be solved with the help of code.</description></item><item><title>Hackathon 2021</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 22:37:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2021/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2021 Friday 10th September &amp;ndash; Sunday 12th September
49-301, Advanced Engineering Building.
Get your tickets now! Facebook event The much awaited UQCS Hackathon is back &amp; better than ever! Taking place from the 10th to 12th of September, this is a great time to learn a new framework, develop your programming and/or design skills, and win some money. Use the link above to buy tickets - make sure to buy them before 22nd August to get a LIMITED EDITION Hackathon 2021 t-shirt for ONLY $5 and early bird tickets for only $10!</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2021</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 08:44:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2021/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2021 (Presented by IMC) 10am &amp;ndash; 4pm, Saturday 20th March The UQCS CodeJam is an individual competitive programming competition hosted each year to put students' programming and problem solving abilities to the test. You'll be given a list of questions to solve, varying in difficulty, with solutions to harder questions earning more points and the highest scoring competitors taking home some sweet prizes. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of fields but all can be solved with the help of code.</description></item><item><title>Hackathon 2020</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:43:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/hackathon-2020/</guid><description>UQCS Hackathon 2020 5pm Friday 16th October &amp;ndash; 8pm Sunday 18th October Get your tickets now! Facebook event Howdy, y'all! We're happy to announce our biggest event of the year, the UQCS Hackathon, will be on October 16th to 18th in Room 301 of the Advanced Engineering Building.
Form a team on Friday night, then spend two days building something cool &amp;mdash; a game, a website, hardware, the sky's the limit.</description></item><item><title>CodeJam 2020</title><link>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 12:16:23 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://uqcs.org/competitions/codejam-2020/</guid><description>UQCS CodeJam 2020 (presented by Atlassian) 10am &amp;ndash; 3:30pm, Saturday 28th March Contest now open on HackerRank.
Sign up to compete and get on the leaderboard! The UQCS CodeJam is an individual competitive programming competition. You get a list of questions to solve varying in difficulty, with harder questions gaining more points. The questions use knowledge from a wide range of fields but all can be solved with the help of code.</description></item></channel></rss>